+237 671 05 32 08

Marc Aurele Djeumou

Junior Data Scientist

Cité des Palmiers, Douala, Cameroun marcdjeumou4@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/marc-djeumou

EDUCATION

Bachelor, Polytechnic of Douala 2024, 3.2

The acquired knowledge in Data Science and AI that I obtain and which define my aptitude now.

SKILLS.

- PhotoShop
- Web development
- Excel
- Google WorkSpace
- Python
- Java

AWARDS

2024 Bachelor

A bachelor's degree in Data Science and Al.

2023 DUT

A diploma where I receive the first knowledge in Computer Science which involve web development and more other.

2021 Baccalaureat

The diploma of my end High School

SUMMARY

About what concerns me, I just want to say that I am an enthusiastic person because I give more relevant determination in all things that I do. In the past my experience was related to the internship that I took in Data Science and AI and also in Web Development, but I also do personal projects in web development, graphic design and for data science, I applied for more challenges to upgrade my skills and stay competitive.

See my personal LinkedIn account at https://www.linkedin.com/in/marc-djeumou

WORK HISTORY

Data Scientist

Jul 2024 - Aug 2024 CAASITECH GROUP, Biyem-ASSI

This position was an internship that was to make us develop and propose AI solutions about a project that the enterprise was taking. This proposition has involved a critical thinking spirit from us to thrive into the problem and find a suitable AI option that can be very often for a good approach.

Web Developer

March 2022 - May 2022 SIMB GROUP, Bonapriso

This other internship has concerned the development of a solution for the group. This solution concerned the conception of a user support about the services that the group proposed.

Web Developer

Aug 2021 - March 2022 LUX WEB SERVICES, Logpom

This was an internship where our task was to develop a web site for the enterprise clients. Then, we were called to work synchronously with other team members to produce a suitable relevant dynamic website that is competitive.